/*
   Wednesday, September 18, 20191:15:59 PM
   User: sa
   Server: DESKTOP-3I72P0N\MAHESHSQL
   Database: IMSDB
   Application: 
*/

'users' table
- Unable to create index 'IX_users'.  
The CREATE UNIQUE INDEX statement terminated because a duplicate key was found for the object name 'dbo.users' and the index name 'IX_users'. The duplicate key value is (mahesh bista).
Could not create constraint or index. See previous errors.
The statement has been terminated.

